<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Krushi Sarthi</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="welcome_to">Welcome to</string>
    <string name="krushi_sarthi">KRUSHI SARTHI</string>
    <string name="sign_up">Sign_up</string>
    <string name="todo">TODO</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">LoginActivity</string>
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="welcome">"Welcome !"</string>
    <string name="invalid_username">Not a valid username</string>
    <string name="invalid_password">Password must be >5 characters</string>
    <string name="login_failed">"Login failed"</string>
    <string name="profile">PROFILE</string>
    <string name="prof">TODO</string>
    <string name="profile1">Profile</string>

    <string name="banana"><b>Introduction</b>
    \nClassical name - Musa Pairadiscaa.
    \nClan - Musseed (Kardali).
    \nParticularly - one-party, molluscum, transmissible, fleshy roots, tropical plants.
    \nNickname - Kardali, Banana, Banana, Rambakkadali, Making.
    \n\n<b>Planting:</b>In terms of area and income, banana is followed by mangoes. India ranks second in the production of bananas. In India, approximately two lakh twenty thousand hectare area is under banana cultivation. Maharashtra is the third largest producer of banana in the field of producing bananas, but in Maharashtra, about 50 percent of Maharashtras first production of commercial production in the business context or in the forecourt is in Maharashtra. Currently, the area is under banana cultivation in the state of Chavala, which covers more than half of the total area. Hence Jalgaon district is considered as a banana banana.
    \n\n<b>Weather:</b>Banana is a tropical coastal fruit and it enjoys a warm and humid climate. Generally, temperatures ranging from 15 to 40 degrees centigrade are good for this crop. If the winter is less than 12 cents per hectare and summer heat is more than 40 cents above the heat, then the crop is affected.
    \n\n<b>Land:</b>Banana crop is rich in organic material, it is very well-suited, well-grounded, or medium-black, with a depth of up to one meter and good drainage of water. Banana plantations are not suitable for salinity.
    \n\n<b>Castes:</b>Banana has 30 to 40 varieties. Suitable stuff for them to survive, eg. Basrai Harisal Lalveel, Whitewella, Matthi, Vlaa Lalkeli and useful varieties for cooking or cooking, for example Rajalei, Anilal and Ornaments are Rangele.
    \n\n<b>Basarai:</b>These castes are named as Khandeshi, Bhusawal, Vankel, Kabuli, Mauritius, Governor, Loton etc. This is the most important thing in the business of Maharashtra. In Maharashtra, 75% of the total banana area is under cultivation. It is a demand for 5 to 6 ft tall, which is rich in excellent quality and good quality, because of which it is more demanding in the market. These varieties provide warm dry weather. This breed reaches less damages.
    \n\n<b>Harisal:</b>The cultivation of this variety is very high in the Vasai region. The height of this caste is up to 4 meters. This species is thicker and the fruits are dull, and this species is durable. Each log contains 150 to 160 fruits and their weight is 28 to 30 kg. This breed manages marine weather.
    \n\n<b>Lalvalachis:</b>This type of plantation is special in Konkan division. The color of this breed is made of reddish-brown, tall tree, fruit is small and thin, and the taste is mango-sweet and color yellow. There are 200 to 225 fruits in this species. Their weight is about 20 to 22 kg in average. This type of cultivation is much higher than other banana varieties in India.
    \n\n<b>Whitewell:</b>This type of tree is tall, smooth, and the fruit is very small and thin, and its neck is damp. Each time, there are 180 fruits and weighing 15 kg. This type of plantation is found in Thane district.
    \n\n<b>Sleep:</b>This breed tree has a height of five meters, a sturdy trunk, a medium-sized fruit and a poultice, its taste is sweet and delicious. These people become victims of this disease. This type of plantation is found in Ratnagiri area.
    \n\n<b>Rajali:</b>This can be found in large quantities in the caste segment of Konkan. The height of this tree is five meters, the fruit is big and long, in length, it has 80 to 90 fruits. Their weight is 12 to 13 kg. This type of raw fruit is suitable for cooking and sowing well.
    \n\n<b>Bakel:</b>This type of tree is 4 to 5 m tall, the fruit is big, like the size of the young, it is straight and peaked. Each louse has 100 to 150 fruits and weighing 18 to 23 kg. This is useful for caste vegetables. This type of plantation is found in Konkan division.
    \n\n<b>Valla:</b>The height of this tree is two meters and the fruit is thick. The taste of the fruit is sweet to the mangoes. Each species has 80 to 100 fruits and their average weight ranges from 12 to 14 kg. This type of plant is especially found in the Deccan Plateau.
    \n\n<b>Red Kyle:</b>The height of this breed tree is 4 to 5 meters. The fruit is bigger and thick and hard. This caste is red and sandalwood and is thick and dense. It also has tastes sweet. There are about 80 to 100 fruits in each country. Their weight ranges from 13 to 18 kg. In all the varieties of banana this caste is known as a batch.
    \n\n<b>Growth:</b>This crop is cultivated by putting the mouthpiece (sweat) from its holes. During the growth of the main tree, many monkeys grow. There are two main types. 1) Combined with sharp edges and busters, 2) Wide round surface of retail stem. The first type of money is used to increase the weight of coconut from half to one kg.
    \n\n<b>Pre-cultivation:</b>Ironing plowing should be done by rowing plowing on the ground. After that, add 100 watt hectare hectare or compost to the mixture.
    \n\n<b>Planting season:</b>Banana seasoning season varies depending on the weather. Because the effect of the haym is on the growth of banana, the time required for the production of fruit and preparation is the same. The cultivation season begins in the Jalgaon district at the beginning of the monsoon. At this time, the climate in this region is warm and humid.
    \n\n<b>Planting method:</b>When planting, we can plant pots of 0.5 x 0.5 x 0.5 m sized pieces by digging or cutting them. The distance between the two plants is 1.25 1.25 or 1.50 1 and 50 meters for the buses.
    \n\n<b>Fertilizers and fertilizers:</b>The roots of this tree are shallow. Their food demand is high. Therefore, it is important to give the nitrogenic installment during the initial period of growth (for the first month).
    \n\n<b>Kid and Disease:</b>In Banana tree, especially Panama disease, hemp flame, etc. are particularly harmful diseases. The worsening of the kidneys is greatly reduced. The information about disease and pest problems is summarized below.
    \n\n<b>Garden care:</b>Keep the ground floor clean and fried. For this, initial scrub should be given. Next should be to paint by hand.
    \nKeep the ground floor clean and fried. For this, initial scrub should be given. Next should be to paint by hand.\nMany bananas are grown in the banana belt. Remove it from time to time.\nApply 4 to 5 months after planting on the soil of the plant.\nProvide support to the plant if necessary.
    \n\n<b>Manure Management:</b>\n<i>Organic fertilizers</i> - 10 kg per plant or 5 kg per plant of vermicelli fertilizer
    \n<i>Bio-fertilizers</i> - Azospirillum - 25 gm per tree and PSB at 25 gram per year during the banana plantation
    \n<i>Chemical fertilizers</i> - 200 gm per plant for banana is recommended to give 40 gm phosphorus and 200 gms of potash. To give them effective fertilization while giving chemical fertilizers to the soil, give deep briquetry to the fertilizers and give them the fertilizer.
    \n\n<b>Water management:</b>Banana crops total 1800 to 2200 min. M Needs water. Drip irrigation is very useful for banana, and it is more suitable for drip irrigation (microtubes) dripper or inline dripper than the micro-tube system. Speed of evaporation, increase in the ratio of land, etc. Banana needs water on matters.
    </string>
    <string name="welcome_to_next_page_wajit">welcome to next page wajit</string>
    <string name="topbg">TODO</string>
</resources>