<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Krushi Sarthi</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="welcome_to">Welcome to</string>
    <string name="krushi_sarthi">KRUSHI SARTHI</string>
    <string name="sign_up">Sign_up</string>
    <string name="todo">TODO</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">LoginActivity</string>
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="welcome">"Welcome !"</string>
    <string name="invalid_username">Not a valid username</string>
    <string name="invalid_password">Password must be >5 characters</string>
    <string name="login_failed">"Login failed"</string>
    <string name="profile">PROFILE</string>
    <string name="prof">TODO</string>
    <string name="profile1">Profile</string>


    <!-- Cropes Description -->
    <string name="bjri">Blocks of earlier crops, garnished with stalks, should clean the soil.Prior to the dynasty, mix 2.5 to 3 tons (5 to 6 bullock pumps) in the field of compost or compost, and in the second frost it should be mixed well in the soil.
        \n\n<b>Sowing:</b> After sowing of summer season of bajra, it is worthwhile in the second fortnight of January to fall in the first fortnight of February.
        If the temperature drops below 10 degrees Celsius, then it is susceptible to damage. If the duration of the sowing is delayed, then the crop comes in flowering after 50 to 55 days of age. If the temperature is higher than 42 degrees C and pollen is likely to die and the production is likely to decrease. Also, late harvesting of the kharif season is delayed due to the delay in summer harvesting.
        \n\n<b>Seed treatment:</b> Use of certified seeds of 1.2 to 1.6 kg per acre. If seeded processed seed is not available, seed should be processed with 20% salt solution (2 kg of salt in 10 liters of water) before sowing for seed disease. Release the seeds of millet in this solution. Drain the fungalized light seeds on the water. Separately, the seeds remaining under the bottom and heavy weight should be washed 2 to 3 times and then dry them in the shade.
        For preventing the prevention of Gosavi disease, seed treatment should be processed in this quantity of seeds in the shade of Metallaxil (35 sd) 6 gm. After chemical processing, the seeds should be processed with zospirillium and phosphorus bacteria for 25 g / kg of each. By 20% savings of nitrogen and phosphorus, 10% increase in production due to the bacterial conservation process. Gravity is uniform and the initial growth of PK is good
        \n\n<b>Sowing:</b> After sowing, after sowing, after sowing, sowing should be done. The distance between the two lines is 30 cm And the difference between two plants is 15 cm Keep it Prepare a flat vapor for 5 to 7 meters long and 3 to 4 meter wide, depending on the land slope. Do it by two wheels, ie fertilizers and seeds can be sown at the same time. Sowing 2 to 3 cm Do not do it at more than the room.
        \n\n<b>Fertilizer Management:</b> At the time of sowing, give 18 kg of nitrogen (39 kg urea), 18 kg of phosphorus (112 kg single super phosphate) and 18 kg potash (30 kg of mutant of potash) per acre. Similarly, after 25 to 30 days after sowing, the second installment should be given to 18 kg of nitrogen (39 kg urea).
        \n\n<b>Cropping:</b> To maintain the correct number of single seedlings, the first rinse should be done after 10 days of sowing and after second sowing, 20 days after sowing, the difference between two plants is 15cm. Keep it 48,000 seedlings per acre are live
        \n\n<b>Inter-school:</b> It is necessary to keep the weeds free from the beginning of 30 days of sowing, because there is competition for getting air, water, nutrients and sunlight between weeds and crops during this period. It is weeding twice and two times according to need. If there is a shortage of labor, then 400 gm of acid per hectare mixed in 200 liters of water per acre, but after sowing, it should be sprayed on ground before planting and weeding in 25-30 days after sowing.
        \n\n<b>Water Management:</b> After 3 to 4 days after sowing, lightly give the first water (mango). After this, according to the condition of the land, in the sensitive condition of the crop, it should be given 5 to 6 water shifts at intervals of 10 to 12 days. If the availability of water is limited, the first stage should be given at the time of arrival of water (20 to 25 days after sowing), second water in the crop area (35 to 45 days after sowing) and third feeding of the grains (60 to 65 days after sowing)
        \n\n<b>Harvesting and production:</b> In the initial phase of crop during the summer season, the growth of the crop is slow due to the low gravity of the sprouting. Therefore it takes more time for the growth of the crop, so summer harvesting season is late 10-15 days after the bajra. The use of summer biscuits hybrid or improved varieties, proper balance sheet and water management, yields up to 14 to 16 quintals per acre. It also provides fodder for milch animals and other animals.\n
    </string>

    <string name="jawari"><b>How to choose varieties of sorghum?</b>\n
        Kharif season is a rainy season. Often, the crop rains when the crop is matured. It affects the crop. As a result, sorghum grows in the jowar and the jowar becomes black. Income also decreases in yield due to increasing production. For this, the varieties used for the Parbhani Shivalata (PVK 801) and Twin Useful Plant PVK 809 for Vardharao Naik Marathwada Agricultural University, Parbhani are used for cultivation.
        Sowing period For the second week of June and the first week of July, it is the perfect period for jawar cultivation. If the duration of the lengthening is delayed then the incidence of cholera increases.Proof of seed
        Hectare 7.5 kg for hybrid sorghum and 10 kg seed of hectare for improved air use.
        \n\n<b>Seed Procedure:</b>\nSeed treatment of Azotobacter bacteria enhancer, nitrogen and phosphorous lymph bacteria, 250 gm per 8-10 kg seed.
        "If delayed planting, prevention of incidence of throat disease, thymathoxemm (70%) should process seed according to 3g / kg Manure Management"
        "Hectury should be well mixed in 5 tons of manure soil. Kharif sorghum is recommended for 80 kg of nitrogen, 40 kg of phosphorus and 40 kg potash per head. Of these, you should give half the nitrogen, complete phosphorus and full potash while sowing. Most likely, the first quantity should be mixed or mixed (150 kg 10-26-26 grams and 50 kg urea). The remaining half-nitrates should be given at 85 kg urea after 30 to 35 days after sowing. Fertilizers should be 5 cm below the seed during sowing. Give it"
        \n\n<b>Inter-school:</b>\nIt is 8-10 days after sowing, it should be filled. 20 cm in 15 days At the distance there is a rape like 1 rope. To handle weeds, weeding twice and two times till crop 40-45 days.
        \n\n<b>Peak protection:</b>\nTo control the debris, spraying of syrupmethrin (10% fluid) in 20 ml per 10 liters of water and after 14 days of sowing, it should be sprayed.
        \n\n<b>Harvesting and Storage:</b>\nHarvest the crop in mature state. Due to having 8% humidity in the grain, it should be stored in dry form. Make a gourd to cook it
    </string>

    <string name="corn"><b>Introduction:</b>
        Rabbi season is the winter … How to make rabbit maize rabbit during this winter season? It is necessary to know this. For rabi corn crops, it is necessary to select medium-to-heavy fertile, well-drained land. The soil in which the organic content is high is suitable for cultivation of land. Generally, the land mass should be between 6.5 to 7.5. Maize crops are also grown in diverse weather conditions.Therefore, corn may be planted at a height of 2700 meters above sea level, but fog may be more prone to corn crops.
        \n\n<b>What is the right temperature for maize?</b>
During rabi season there is an increase in the temperature, so there is a decrease in temperature. But, for the corn crop, the average 18 to 20 degrees. Temperatures can be fruitful.
During the Rabi season the temperature of the night is mild and decreases the decrease in the amount of light decreased due to light, respiratory failure.
Also, the process of photosynthesis becomes faster and faster due to the length, width, structure of the leaf and the intense sunlight for 7-8 hours, which increases the product by increasing the duration of the crop.
\n\n<b>How Important Is Water Management?</b>
Rabi season can be said to be less humid because the dew falls on the night due to cold.
Due to mild temperatures and low humidity in the rabi season, the incidence of diseases and pests is very less.
In the rabi season the plant number can be kept in the proper quantity due to land and water management, as well as lower incidence of diseases and pests.
If the weeds get proper control, the effectiveness of the chemical fertilizers used will increase.
\n\n<b>How to sow?</b>
In rabi season, sowing of maize under 60 cm in the bag, at half the height of half an inch, in between 18 to 20 cm, two seeds four to five cm. Do it by biting deep.
If the sowing is done on the south side of the sari, the sunlight germination becomes better and the growth of the crops is strong.
If it is planned in the sowing, it will get about 90,000 seedlings per hectare and result in higher yields.
\n\n<b>What care should be taken to control disease?
</b>
Before sowing, two to two and a half grams of thyroid juice is controlled by fungicide per kg of seeds.
Also, if the Azotobacter bacterial breeding grows 15 grams per kilogram of seeds, then there will be five percent increase in production.
\n\n<b>How to use fertilizers?</b>

Chemical fertilization is used during sowing.
At the time of sowing, the chemical fertilizers should be mixed in 5 to 7 cm area and soil well.
Once the harvest is successful, then in the vertical peak, the nitrogen fertilizer (urea) is 10-12 cm. Give it away from the line and give it water immediately.
Water should be given at an interval of 10 to 12 days according to the condition of the soil.
After plucking maize after ten days, keep a single vigorous rope on a four foot


    </string>

    <string name="pieon">

    </string>

    <string name="wheat"><b>The technique is the cultivation of wheat
</b>Presently the work of farmers is going on for rabbis everywhere. The main crop of rabi season is wheat. Wheat production is widely grown in Punjab in India. The rabbi season is the season of cold weather, it should not be a waste. The wheat crop provides cool and dry weather. The higher the chill and the more they survive, the better the growth of the wheat crop. If wheat crop gets more than 100 days in cold weather, production can get more and better qualitThat is why cold weather is necessary for wheat crop.
\n\n<b>Planting:-</b>
There are some rules in the agricultural field to take any crop. Therefore, the season of each crop is fixed. The farming land and the method of harvesting crops that play a major role in this. In the case of wheat, wheat is cultivated in both the cultivation and in the garden. In this case, if considered for horticulture, then it is necessary to have good drainage ground. Such a land in which the moisture can survive for long periods of time. Therefore, select the best quality land for the cultivation.
\n\n<b>Pre-Educative:-</b>
Proper and adequate cultivation is necessary for the wheat crop to grow well. Because, the root of the wheat crop is 60 to 75 cm. Because of the fact that a good crop of land is going to be harvested, good farm work is needed. Therefore, after harvesting the kharif season and iron-plow with 15-20 cm. Planting deep land should be given and after 3 to 4 times the diversification should be given. In this way cultivation can be done to clean the land from the earlier crop dust and weeds.
If it is well planted during Kharipa, it can be beneficial to fry the land by three to four shifts of clay.
\n\n<b>Sowing:-</b>
October is very good for wheat sowing. Sowing should be done in the second fortnight of October. However, if the sowing of horticultural wheat is to be sown, the correct time is the first fortnight of November. During this period, the yield of wheat is better if sowing is done. Horticultural wheat can be sown late, but the result is on the production.
\n\n<b>What is the number of seedlings?</b>\n
If you want more product then it is important how much plant you plant in the soil. Therefore, the number of seedlings is important. If there is a total number of seedlings in the field of about 20 to 22 lakhs per hectare, the product can get better. For this, use 100 to 125 kg of seed per hectare. For late sowing, use 125-150 kg seed per hectare. Seedlings of 75 to 100 kg of hectare for cumin seed should be used for sowing.
\n\n<b>How to plan for fertilizer?</b>
There is a need for food grains for horticultural and dry-wheat wheat. Hence, chemical fertilizer planning is important. For timely sowing 50:50:50 kg nitrogen, phosphorus, potash per hectare and 50 kg of nitrogen should be given 21 days after sowing. For late sowing should be given 40:40:40 kg nitrogen, potash per hectare.
In this way, if wheat is sown by proper planning, good and quality product can be obtained. As a result, the farmers need the information before harves


    </string>

    <string name="watana"><b>Weather and Land</b>This crop benefits much from the cold.
The average temperature of the month is 10 to 20 degrees. Have to be
For seed germination to grow 22 degrees Temperature is very favorable.
Choose ground, medium, fertile, well-drained water, deep land for planting of pea crop.
The content of the soil should be 6 to 7.5.
\n\n<b>Forever</b>
Due to good soil cultivation, the root growth of the plant is very fast.
Make parallel and frosted fields.
Before planting, add ten tons of manure to each hectare.
Before planting, apply 3 gms of carbendazim per kg of seeds to the seeds.
Prior to cultivation, soil testing should be given to 15 kg of nitrogen, 60 kg of phosphorus and 60 kg potash.
\n\n<b>Planting:</b>
Planting can be done from the first fortnight of October to the first fortnight of November.
For this crop 50-75 kg seed should be used for sowing.
Planting 30 x 15 cm in vermilion or flat bed Do it at intervals.
Due to the seed b-gibleic acid planted in 100 ppm of acid, dung for 12 hours and after planting, the production of legumes increases.
For seed processing, rye seeds should be used for seeding.
\n\n<b>Manure Management:</b>
At the time of cultivation under oligarchy, the fertilizer should be given at 50:75:50 per ha, and 25 kg of nitrate per month. Eight to ten hectare hectares of well-sown cultivation before planting and after planting.
Due to the relocation of nitrogen in the crop soil, the quantity of nitrogen fertilizers should be reduced.
8 cm around the plant, without throwing it on the ground. Spacing around the sphere The presence of nitrogenous fertilizers and caterpillars affects the germination of the seeds.
\n\n<b>Castes and their features:</b>
\n<b>Water management:</b>
This breed has boots. This is going to be coming soon. Grassed with green and soft cloth, it was fully grown in 30-35 days after planting. Peanuts need to be single. The length of the beans is seven to eight centimeters, dark green in color.
\n<b>Pest and diseases management:</b>
Early coming, the color of the veal is blue-green. Height of the tree 40-45 cm Is there. The flowering was in 38 days. The beans are single and green, while the beans have five or six grains.
\n<i>Unassuming-</i>
The height of the plant is 35-40 cm, dark green color, the flowers come singly. Seedling green green, seven to eight cm Extracts in long and short periods of 58 to 60 days. This trend is ideal for beginning of October.
\n<i>Alaska-</i>
This type of tree is medium height and the tree needs double legumes. Flowering was in 55-60 days. The color of the legume is light green, the legume is straight, usually nine cms. There are six to seven grains in long and legume.
\n<i>Meteor-</i>
It is a product that is growing and producing more. Dead lumps and pods are resistant to lactic acid. The incidence of brownie disease is less visible.
\n\n<i>Bonwheel-</i>
This crop needs less water than other vegetable crops.
Give light to the crops after planting.
The second shift in the water should be given during the flowering period and the third leg may be filled with grains.
Regular water supply should be given if the soil is lightly sand.
\n\n<i>Aparna-</i>
\n<i>Disease-</i>
\nBhuri, Karpa:The disease is very high on this crop. For this control, fertilize the caratene / sulfur / Bavistin in 2.5 g / 1 liter of water.
Dots on the leaves / ribs: Diethen M-45 g / liter water for this disease

\nDying:To control the disease, process the thyroid of 4g / kg seed
\nInsect:On this crop, there are infested pests of goose weevil, legumes, pests, larvae, mawa, tuduttadesi, legumes and pests.
To control their monocrotophos mixed with 1.5 ml / liters of water.
\nHarvesting and production:The pea is prepared for 45 to 65 days.
By changing the dark green color of the legume, they are light green and green
Harvesting is completed in 3 to 4 breaks. The harvest season runs for 3 to 4 weeks.
Early varieties of green pods produce 10-15 quintals of acreage and a mid-yearly breed production ranges between 20 to 25 quintals and late varieties from 30 to 40 quintals of produce.
The proportion of legume is 40 to 45 percent.
It is convenient to chop twice a week.

    </string>

    <string name="mung">
<b>Land:</b>
In general it can be taken in all types of soil drainage. It can be harvested in medium to heavy soil.
\n\n<b>Climate:</b>
This crop is warm and nutritious, and this crop is well grown in temperature of 21 degrees to 35 degrees. 750 to 9 00 min. I In the rainy areas, there is good production of mung bean crops. The cold winter does not count this crop.
\n\n<b>Pre-cultivation:</b>
After removing the earlier crop, the ground should be plucked with iron plow, and after plowing, give two sparrows.
\n\n<b>Bacterial Enhancer:</b>
If sowing after sowing the seeds of Riazobium bacteria before sowing, the product will increase by 15 to 20%.
\n\n<b>Seed Procedure: </b>
Mucus is affected by insect bacterial disease in plants. To prevent damage from this disease, seed must be processed according to sowing of thyroid or Bavistin one to 3 g / kg of fungicide.
\n\n<b>Sowing:</b>
Kharif mug sowing should be done as soon as the monsoon starts. Sowing should be done differently. Seed 4c I In the room The difference between the two lines is 30 cm. I Keeping the seeds should be 12 to 15 kg. In the Kharif season the moong peak is ready for 60 to 70 days. Rabi season should be sown from October 25 to November 9. Rabi mug crops are generally prepared in about 110 days. During the summer season, the pea should be sown in the first week of March. During the summer season the crop is ready for 60 to 65 days.
\n\n<b>Improved varieties:</b>
Old varieties of <i>Jalgaon 781</i> and <i>Kopargaon</i> in Maharashtra are under khair for many years. Apart from this, <i>TA</i> has been jointly organized by the joint efforts of Bhabha Atomic Research in Punjabrao Agricultural University in Akola. P-7 varieties have been transmitted, this variety gives 24% more production than Coppergaon, and this disease is also more resistant to immunity. Besides, Mahatma Krishi Vidyapeeth Rahuri distributed Mung-2 varieties for western Maharashtra for Kharif season.
Is there. The varieties <i>S - 8</i> and <i>Pusa Vaishakhi</i> are popular for summer mugs.\nOld varieties of <i>Jalgaon</i> 781 and <i>Kopargaon</i> in Maharashtra are under khair for many years. Apart from this, <i>TA</i> has been jointly organized by the joint efforts of Bhabha Atomic Research in Punjabrao Agricultural University in Akola. P-7 varieties have been transmitted, this variety gives 24% more production than Coppergaon, and this disease is also more resistant to immunity. Besides, Mahatma Krishi Vidyapeeth Rahuri distributed Mung-2 varieties for western Maharashtra for Kharif season.
Is there. The varieties <i>S - 8</i> and <i>Pusa Vaishakhi</i> are popular for summer mugs.

    </string>

    <string name="cotton">

    </string>


    <!-- Vegetables Description -->

    <string name="tomato"><b>Introduction:</b>
        \nIn Maharashtra, there are approximately 29,190 hectare area under tomato cultivation. Nashik, Pune, Satara, Ahmednagar, Nagpur, Sangli are important districts of Maharashtra producing tomato. Tomatoes are the main fruit of the farmers of Maharashtra, as the three varieties are cultivated in tomato crop in Kharif and Rabi summer season. Since tomato is widely available in the head protector food, then the importance of diet of tomatoes is unique. Tomato A, B and C vitamins and mineral nutrients like lime, iron etc are also adequate in tomatoes.Raw or reddish-white fruits of tomatoes are used for vegetable or salad. It can also be made from tomatoes-frozen fruits like soup, pickle, sauce, ketchup, jam, juice etc. This has led to the increased industrial importance of tomatoes.
        \n\n<b>Weather:</b>
        \nAlthough tomato is a hot weather crop, tomato is cultivated throughout the year in Maharashtra. If there is excessive cold, tomato tree growth Fluctuations in temperature fluctuate effect. The plant growth was good in temperature ranging from 13 to 38 Celsius. Flowers and fruits are good. If the temperature of the night is between 18 to 20 Celsius, then the fruit of tomato is good. The liquepopne hectare, which gives attractive color to the fruits, pigment is widely prepared at temperatures ranging from 26 to 32 cents. The combined results of temperature, sunlight and humidity are on the growth of the crop. Tomato Crop yields a good yield as compared to 20 to 32 degrees Celsius, 11 to 12 hours of clean sunshine and 60 to 75 percent of the humidity.
        \n\n<b>Land:</b>
        \nMedium to heavy plantation is suitable for tomato crop. Fruits in light soil get ready early, water drains get better And the growth of the crops was good. But in such a land, organic fertilizers have to be filled up and there is a need for frequent watering. The medium content of the soil should be 6 to 8.
        \n\n<b>Predetermined:</b>
        \nAfter giving the plowing of the fields, plowing should be broken and wrapped. For the cultivation of 30-40 units of hectare in the soil, the spacing between the two lines should be 60 to 90cm and the difference between the two plants should be 45 to 60cm. For the Kharif and winter season, cultivate at 90 x 60 cm distance and 60 to 45 cm distance for the summer season.
        \n\n<b>Season:</b>
        \nKharif - in June, J. B. Peraway.
        Rabbi (winter season) September, in the month of October sow seed.
        Summer season - in December, January will be sown
        The proportion of seeds is 400 to 500 gm of hectare tomato crop.
        \n\n<b>Improved varieties:</b>
        \nThe varieties of tomato varieties suitable for cultivation in Maharashtra are as follows.
        \nPusa Ruby: It can be taken in three seasons. After the cultivation, fruits can be harvested from 45 to 90 days after planting. Fruit furrows are shaped like red sand. Hectare production 325 quintals
        \nPusa Gaurav: This caste shrub is growing fast. The fruits become yellowish crimson after lubrication. The traffic is right. Hectare yield 400 quintals
        \nPusa Shital: Planting is suitable for the winter season, and the fruits are rounded red in color. Hectare yield 350 quintals
        \nArka Gaurav: The fruit is dark red fleshy and comfortable. Hectare production up to 350 quintals
        \nRoma: The trees are small and shrubbery and it is suitable for transport because it is long and thick in size. Hectare production is 25 tons.Rupali, Vaishali, Bhagyashree, Arka Vikas, Pusa Early Dwarf etc. Caste is cultivated.
        \n\n<b>Planting:</b>
        \nSeeds should be sown on the bed. Before preparing the bed plant, make sure to double the soil by placing it 2, 3. Gadai wafa is 1m The width should be 3m long and 15cm high. Grind 1 gram Fenugreek, add 50 grams of soyafa and make the steam flat with the hand. Before sowing, wash 3 gm of thyroid fungicide. Planting of seeds should be planted with parallel fingers by cutting the waist and covering it with soil. Water should be provided to the flyer. After germination of seed, after 10 to 12 days, give two grams of poultry in two rows and give 10 gm for each leaflet. Keep the steam in the weasel. To control the flowering and crushing disease, after splitting 15 days after seedling, sprinkle 12-20 ml of monocrotocus and 25 gm of dyhenene M-45 in 10 liters of water. The next two sprays should be done at intervals of 10 days. After 25 to 30 days of sowing, it is generally after seedlings are raised to 12 to 15 cm then the seedlings should be restored to the entire world. Give water to the vapor a day before planting the seedlings. Therefore, the seedlings of seedlings are easily accessible without roots. Planting of plants should always be done in the evening or after the reduction.
        \n\n<b>Chemical fertilizers:</b>
        \n200-100-100 for the right varieties and 300-150-150 kg of nitrogen, phosphoric powder for hybrid varieties. Half of the nitrogen should be given at the time of cultivation and 40 days after planting.
        \n\n<b>Water management:</b>
        \nProvide light water for 3 to 4 days after planting. And then after 8 to 10 days, give another water. In the rainy season, tomato crop should be given at intervals of 8 to 10 days during the monsoon season, and during winter season 5 to 7 days intervals and summer season should be given to the plants for 3 to 4 days intervals. Always give light water to heavy black soil. Regular water supply is important when the crop is blooming and fruit growth. Otherwise the fluffy, frying of fruit, is likely to dissipate like this. In the summer, if it gives a traditional method of watering tomatoes, it needs 77 hectare of water. If water is given by drip irrigation, it needs 56 hectare of water. Due to drip irrigation, water yields 50 to 55 percent and yields 40 percent increase.
        \n\n<b>Inter-school:</b>
        \nRemove weeds by regular weeding. Take care that weeds do not hurt the root cause. So that it can have adverse effects on the yield.
        \n\n<b>Turn and garden support:</b>
        \nThe tomato crop is weak and they are weak because they need support. By supporting, the growth of the trees and the branches was good. The fruit takes a lot. Fruits, leaves and branches are not exposed to land or water. This reduces the number of fruit rot and disease. Fertilizer, spraying, etc. Work can be done easily. Tomato trees can be supported in two ways. 1. Each plant should be made to stick a stick of one to two meters long and stick a stick with a sticky stick. 2. In this case, the tart is made using a star and bamboo or sticks. And trees are grown on the basis of these tapes. Take the rate of every 10 feet in front of the saree and apply it to the height of two meters in height and with a thick semi-thickness, it should be raised in both directions. Bundle with a stellar string in front of each stem and tie it with stringed instruments. After that, build a gauge of 45 gm from the ground and sew each stitch by siege and stretch it to the other end, thus the second 90 cm and the third at 120 cm distance. These branches should be made of twine or nylon ropes. To make a tomato cage, it is necessary to turn the tree around.
        \n\n<b>Disease and kidney disease:</b>
        \nDisease Karpa: This disease can occur in any condition of tree growth. The leaves in the disease fall on the stalks and brown spots on it.
        \nRemedies: Spread the dyhemum M45, 25 liters in 10 liters of water, and mix it well. Spraying should be done at intervals of 10-15 days.
    </string>

    <string name="chilli"><b>Introduction:</b>
Chillies are essential for daily diet. In the market there is a demand for green chillies throughout the year. Apart from this, there is a good demand from Indian chillies abroad too. Maharashtra pepper is cultivated on approximately one lakh hectare area. 68% of the area under Chilli area of Maharashtra is Nanded Jalgaon Dhule Solapur Kolhapur Nagpur Amravati Chandrapur is located in Osmanabad district. Chilli a And Cholesterol-rich diet is included in a great amount of vitamins. Chilli hectare is a major spice crop due to pungency and taste. Pepper also has medicinal use.
\n\n<b>Weather: </b>
In hot and humid climate, the good growth of the chilli crop gets better. Chilli Crop can be planted during the monsoon, summer and winter season. If there is excessive rainfall and a cloudy weather in the monsoon, then the fungus tumors are high. Leaves and fruits are scorched.
Chilli has less than 40 inches of rain. Good chilly trees and fruit growth were better than 25 to 30 Celsius. And there is also a lot of product. Due to variability in temperature, the fruit flora is saliva. And income is reduced. The germination of the seeds was good for the temperature of 18 to 27 Celsius.
\n\n<b>Land: </b>
Chilli crop is good for moderately heavy soil due to the high drainage of water. Chilli crop gets better when it is used in proper quantity of organic fertilizers. Chilli is not picked for proper soil untreated ground. In the monsoon and horticultural chilli, select medium black and water well drained area. Grow the pepper in medium to heavy soil in the summer. Chilli crop is also good in limestone soil.
\n\n<b>Season:</b>
Kharif crop should be planted in the month of june, july and summer crop in the month of January.
\n\n<b>Varieties:</b>
Pusa flame: This variety is good for green chillies and these species are covered with bulk and lot of branches. Fruits are usually 10 to 12 cm long, and horizontally crisp on the fruit. The fruit is heavy and very scaly. Grown fruits are red in color. Pant C - 1: It is good to go green and red pepper products. The fruits of this species are vomiting. Fruit is found in attractive red color after the chilli. The fruit is 8 to 10 cm long and the year is thick. The ratio of fruit bone is high and the hepatic antibody is resistant.
Sankeshwari 32 - This type of tree is tall. Chilli is 20 to 25 cm long and has a thin lid. There are curls on the bridegroom. The color of the dried dead color is red.

G-2, G-3, G-4, G-5 species of this type are lighted. There are better varieties of this chilli product. The fruit length is 5 to 8 cm and the color of the fruit is red.
\n\n<b>Musalwadi:</b>
This type of tree grows tall. It is good for Kharif season and it suffers from diseases like goose, brown and diabetic.
Pusa Evergreen - This type of tree is tall and leaves are broader than other varieties. Seasoned chillies are bright red. The average yield of these varieties of green chillies is one to ten to ten tons and dried pepper yields one and a half to two tons. It is resistant to Dry Mawa Koli insects as well as diabetic and viral diseases.

    </string>

    <string name="potato"><b>Introduction:</b>
        \nPotato is grown in the district of Pune, Satara, Nashik, Ahmednagar, Beed, Aurangabad and Nagpur. Potato contains plenty of minerals such as proteins, lime, phosphorus, B and C vitamins. Potato is widely used in many industries without foodstuffs.
        \n\n<b>Weather:</b>
        \nPotato is a crop in cold weather. The average temperature is 16 to 21 degrees Celsius. During the beginning of the crop, there are 24 celsius nutrients which are favorable to 20 celsius during the feeding season. During cold weather and hot potatoes during the cultivation of potatoes, the cold weather is the result of this crop.
        \n\n<b>Land:</b>
        \nPotato can be planted in a medium squeeze soil. The land should be well-rounded and well-researched. The content of the soil should be between 6 and 8.
        \n\n<b>Predetermined:</b>
        \nPlow plow 20 to 25 cms thick. Summer heat should be given to the ground throughout the month. Again, plowing 1 horizontal should be done. To break the clay and to bring the land at the same level, let the land be fried by two or three strands of cloves, spreading 50 well-sized weeds in the soil.
        \n\n<b>Planting season:</b>
        \nPotato plantation is done in the month of June, Kharif and during the rabi season in October, November.
        \n\n<b>Varieties:</b>
        \nKufri early - is being prepared in 65 to 80 days and is being taken in kharif and rabi season. These varieties of potatoes are very large in white spots. This kind of potato is good for storing. Hectare production is 200 to 250 quintals. Kufri Chandramukhi - The caste is ready for 90 to 100 days. This type of potato is long and light green in color. Its great to be in storage. Hectare yields up to 250 quintals.
        \n\n<b>Kufari Sinduri:</b>
        \nThis being between 120 to 135 days is ready. This type of color is light red and the potatoes are medium and round. This is good for hoarding. Hectare yields up to 300 quintals.
        \n\n<b>Seed yield:</b>
        \nSeeds should be of excellent quality. The cultivation of 15 to 20 quintals of seed per hectare is sufficient. Before planting, take 30 grams of Captain Captain and 10 grams of Baviston for 10 liters of water and dip it after planting.
        \n\n<b>Planting:</b>
        \nThe weight of the average weight should be 25 to 30 grams. According to the size of the potato, the distance between two lines should be between 45 and 60 cm and the distance between the two bands should be 15 to 20 cm. With the help of the tractor, plant all the herbs in the top.
        \n\n<b>Fertilizers and water management:</b>
        \nBefore planting potato, there is a requirement of 100 kg of nitrogen and 60 kg of power. Give second dose of 50 kg per hectare of Nitrogen for 1 month after cultivation. Because the children of potato are growing in the upper layers of the soil, this crop should be given less water at the time of water level. The first of the cultivation Lighten the water. When the soil of the adjoining area starts to fizzle and give potato to the potato, water should be given at 6 to 8 days later. Reduce the water table after the growth of the crop.
        \n\n<b>Inter-school:</b>
        \nIt is an important task to emphasize the weeding and weeding in the intermacie of potato. After weeding three times four times, keep the ground groundnut. Due to the second installment of the fertilizer, soil should be added to the soil.
        \n\n<b>Diseases and pests:</b>
        \nKarpa -    The leaves fall through black dots on the leaves. There are deep thoracic plaques on the potato.
        \nRemedy - 30 gm of diaxene mixed in 10 liters of water should be sprayed.
        \nDying -    Large trees look yellow and clusters:
        \nThere is an increase in fungus on the ground floor under the stove. Due to the frequent use of crops and regular water changes, the disease is ending. If seeds are mixed with naphthalene or formalin (1:50), seeds of disease die.Charcoal disease or cough disease - The disease spreads from the soil. If the temperature of the soil is more than 32 celsius, it is useful for the disease. Due to this disease, there is no stocking of potatoes. Before the temperature of the ground should rise to 32 celsius, potato should be cut or kept low by keeping the water low.
        \n\n<b>Pest:</b>
        \nStalked larvae - Rakhi-colored coconut grows in the night at night. Leaves and ravenous stalks eat.
        \nRemedies -  For the disposal of this pest, chlorade M 5% powder should be used for 50 kg of ground water in the evening.
        \nMoiva and Tudutude -  This pest absorbs the food in the pan. So the leaves fall yellow. After 15 days of cultivation, methyl dynamite mixed in 10 ml 10 liters of water or phosphomidon 85w MC 10 ml in 10 liters of water.
        \nPotato Potato - This kidney damages the potato. This pest started from the field. Paratukasana is seen in the storage period. This pestle falls into the stomach and stomach. Algae enters potato and eats the inner part.
        \nRemedies – Carbaryl 50 WP for the prevention of this pest. 1.5 kg fatty mixed with 750 water.
        \n\n<b>Harvesting and production:</b>
        \nIf using potato crop using all the improved techniques, early varieties can be produced in 200 quintals of hectare and production of late varieties can be upto 250 to 300 quintals of hectare.
    </string>

    <string name="fenugreek"><b>Introduction:</b>
\n•	Due to the various properties of fenugreek,there is good demand in fertile urban areas.
\n•	In view of this, fenugreek seeds are grown in large part of the city.For fenugreek leaves and stalking vegetables, the seeds are used in a lot of spices and pickles.
\n•	There are adequate amounts of A, B and C vitamins as well as proteins, magnesium, phosphorus, potassium and iron in fenugreek.
\n•	Fenugreek has various medicinal properties. Fenugreek is digestive, increasing the efficiency of the liver and pliha. So, the efficiency of the pc process increases.
        \n\n<b>Weather:</b>
        \n•	Although fenugreek is a cold weather, it is also good in hot weather.
        \n•	Especially for musk fertile cold weather.
        \n•	The fenugreek seeds can be harvested in both kharif and rabi season.
        \n\n<b>Land:</b>
        \n•	Fenugreek is perfectly suitable in the silt field.
        \n•	The soil from moderately to tight, well-drained water and soil between Haminis clay 6 to 7 is more than fenugreek.
        \n\n<b>Modified Castes:</b>
        \n1. Musk
        \n2. Pusa Early Bunching
        \n3. R. M. T-1
        \n4. Fenugreek no 47

    </string>

    <string name="ladyfinger"><b>Introduction:</b>
        \nWholeel is a very good fruit. Calciel and iodine in the olive oil are rich in mangroves and citrus fruits. In Maharashtra, under okra 8190 hectare area is under cultivation. Okra is harvested throughout the year.
        \n\n<b>Land and climate: </b>
        \nThe okra can be grown in light medium and heavy soil. But there should be good drainage of water. While okra is grown throughout the year, it is better to harvest the crop during kharif and summer season. Picasis is good for temperature of 20 to 40 Celsius. While there is scarcity of water, okra is better than other vegetables. In the summer when the vegetable is cooking, the ladys finger is very demanding in the market.
        \n\n<b>Varieties: </b>
        \nPusa Savani Selection 2-2 Flour Utkarsha, Parbhani Revolution, Arka Annamika are suitable for cultivation of improved varieties.
        \n\n<b>The ratio of seeds:</b>
        \nIn Kharif season, the yield of 8 kg of hectare and 10 kg of seed in the summer is enough. Pour 3g of thyme before sowing to 1 kg seed.
        \n\n<b>Pre-mature and planted:</b>
        \nLand cultivation should be grounded by one acre and two cloves and ground 50 kg of groundnut and third coriander mixed with hectare. In the kharif season for sowing, keep the distance between two lines in 60 cm. And keep it 45 cm in the summer. Between two lines of two lines in a line, keep the two biennial beads in place of B. Put the cake in the summer and bake it with the pot. After sowing, after the arrival of the wafsa, sow the seed.
        \n\n<b>Fertilizers and water management:</b>
        \nAt the time of sowing, mix the quantity of 50-50-50 kg of nitrogen, phosphorus and Palaash in the soil and give the second installment of 50 kg nitrogen in the month of one month after sowing. Give light water after sowing. After that, the water cover at intervals of 5 to 7 days.
        \n\n<b>Inter-school:</b>
        \nAfter weeding a hazard and two, weave the weeds in the field.
        \n\n<b>Disease and kidney disease:</b>
        \nBhuri: Bhairy Disease is mainly seen on Bhandi Disease.
        \nRemedy: For the control of this disease, spray sulfur mixed with water, 1 kg or DietaMine 45, 1250g in 500 liters of water per hectare.
        \nKid: Bhindi Pikas Mawa Tudutude Sundemli Red Koli is a pest of the insects.
        \nRemedies: For control of these pests, 35cc endosulphan 1248 ml or 35 mc 200 C of 200 ml of Syfmetheiterin mixed with 500 liters of water per hectare. After the first spraying, after 15 days, the spraying of spraying after 15 days should be done at intervals of 15 days.
        \n\n<b>Harvesting and production: </b>
        \nAfter harvest, after 55 to 60 days of fruit harvesting are ready. Fruits are harvested every 3 to 4 days. Parbhani revolution can not be broken by the disease due to illness, fruits can be harvested for 3 to 4 weeks longer than other varieties. So there is more production. During the kharif season, green fruit yields 105 to 115 quintals per hectare whereas in the summer season it is 75 to 85 quintals.

    </string>

    <string name="carrot"><b>Introduction:</b>
The use of carrots is used for the diet as a vegetable or raw food. Animal feeding is also done. Because of high levels of life in Gajra, regular use of the diet does not make eye care impaired. Used for cooking soup, salad, pickle, light, jam etc. The carrots are dried and dried by carrots.
Weather and Land
Carrot is a growing crop in cold weather. To get the attractive colors of Gajra, the temperature is 15-20 degrees. Have to be From 10 to 15 degrees The temperature is 20 to 25 degrees. If planting of carrots at the end of October and the first week of November, the size and color of the plant is good. But it can be done from September to December. For better growth, from 18 to 24 degrees. The temperature is very nutritious.
Carrot is a growing root in the soil. Therefore, the land selected for the cultivation of gajra should be made of soft soap and should be able to cultivate heavy land cultivation and make the land wet. For Gajra cultivation, select land that is deep fried with sesame seeds and fine drainage of water.
\n\n<b>Improved breeds:</b>
Pusa Kaiser, Nantis, Pusa Mandhali are the revised varieties of Gajar.
\n\n<b>Season:</b>
Garajra is cultivated in Kharif and rabi season in Maharashtra. The carrots in rabbi season are very sweet and very good quality. Rabi season seasoning, from August to decibhar, the kharif season is cultivated from June to July.
\n\n<b>Method of planting:</b>
 The ground stands for the cultivation of gajar - to plow the threshing. Flat the ground. B above the other Keeping the difference between the two wires should be 45 cm, while sowing the seed with a towel, pull it at 30 to 45 cm distance and plant it with a token method of 15 cm distance from both sides. Applying sowing seeds should be between 30 to 45 cm in two lines, after which the two seedlings are divided in 8 Keep cm For one hectare area, about 4 to 6 kg of saplings are required for the garage. To sow the seed before sowing, it takes 12-15 days after sowing. This time can be reduced by keeping seeds in the water 24 hours before sowing.
\n\n<b>Pests and their control:</b>
Sandy weevil (carat vival), on the car\you wills crop, is a pest of six dots, and it is a pest of ruffia. Spraying of 10 ml of melathion in 10 liters of water for the control of pests and weeds and weeds. The adult fur of the insect pests is green from green to black color. The larvae of this kidney is white in color and the roots of the carrot are frozen .In the eating and eating the inner part, the roots of the carrots become weird and weird. Gazera leaves dry up For the control of this pest, add 3 ml of diazepthaate mixed in 10 liters of water. The carrot crop contains carp, bhuri, dots on dead leaves, etc.
        \n\n<b>Harvesting production and sale:</b>
 Garlic harvesting can be done in 70 to 90 days after the sowing of seeds. To make the Gajra better, stop the irrigation of the crop for 15 to 20 days before harvesting. Dug the cage with a cushioned hand or a carpet by a crib. Cut off the leaves from the carrots and wash the carrots clean with water. Separate small cargo size. The production of the garage produces 8 to 10 tons of hectare.


    </string>

    <string name="spinach"><b>Introduction:</b>
        \n•	The parental origin is considered to be India.Spinach is known as a part of Indian food culture.
        \n•	Various recipes like spinach, almonds, soup, bhaji are prepared from the parents.here are plenty of \you willA\you will and \you willC\you will vitamins in the parent.
        \n•	Besides, there is a great combination of iron, calcium, potassium, sulfur, sour, and protein.
        \n•	That is why parents have a good market in this market.
        \n•	It will be beneficial for the farmers to know about how to \you willplanting spinach\you will.
        \n\n<b>Land:</b>
        \n	Parental cultivation can be done in all types of soil.
        \n	The poorly drained clay land manages the parents.
        \n	The land should be 7 for cultivation of parents.
        \n	Although the soil is slightly alkalized, it can bear the crop of the parents.
        \n\n<b>Weather:</b>
        \nParents are the all-weather crop. However, the winter season is good for parents. With the temperature of about 35 to 40 degrees Celsius, the leaves of the stem thick and tastes are suitable. The crop also comes from early flowering.
        \n\n<b>Modified Castes:</b>
        \n	1. Pusa Jyoti
        \n  2. Oligreen
        \n  3. Pant composite
        \n  4. Pusa green
        \n\n<b>Planting:</b>
        \n	After 2-3 times the soil is mixed with 30 to 35 tons of fertilizers in the soil.
        \n	3 x 1 m for cultivation Make a flat-sized dish.
        \n	Remove the slope of 1 to 1.5 cm depth from 15 to 20 cm distance and cover the soil with soil.
        \n	Or throw the seeds uniformly. About 8 to 10 kg of seeds are required for this.
        \n\n<b>Manure Management:</b>
        \n30-35 tonnes of manure, 40 kg nitrogen, 40 kg of phosphorus and 40 kg per hectare per hectare.
    	25 kg of nitrogen should be given after each harvest. If there is 1 to 2 percent urea spraying, the product increases.
        \n\n<b>Water Planning:</b>
        \n	Water should be given at intervals of 3 to 4 days according to soil moisture.
        \n\n<b>Inter-school:</b>
        \n	Arrange it at the time of weed, 2-3 needles should be done as per requirement.
        \n\n<b>Harvesting:</b>
        \n1.	Harvested with fully grown fresh and tender leaves. First weeding should be done 3-4 weeks after sowing.
        \n2.	Later layers should be done at intervals of 15 days.
        \n\n<b>Production:</b>
        \nParents receive 15 to 20 tons of hectare per hectare.

    </string>

    <string name="onion"><b>Introduction:</b>
        \n Onion is the most important vegetable crop in business. Onion is widely used in the diet of Indians. Maharashtra tops the field in terms of area and production in the state of Onion Pikvina. Onion plantation is cultivated in about 1.00 lakh hectares of Maharashtra. Nashik, Pune, Solapur, Jalgaon, Dhule, Ahmednagar are famous for the production of onion in the district.Also on Marathwada Vidarbha and Konkan, some of the districts are planted onions. Nashik district is famous for its growing onion in India, not in Maharashtra. Out of total production, 37% of Maharashtra and 10% of India\you wills onion production is produced in Nashik district alone.
        \n\n<b>Weather:</b>
        \nOnion is a crop of winter season, and in mild climate of Maharashtra 2 to 3 crops of onion are taken. The weather gets cold for 1 to 2 months from onion cultivation. Temperature increase in onion production is useful for growing onion.
        \n\n<b>Land:</b>
        \nThe moderate to the fine earth which is full of organic water rich in surface water and organic fertilizers, has good human resources.
        \n\n<b>Forever:</b>
        \nAfter plowing the horizontal plinth of the ground, the family should be crushed and crushed. Mix 40-50 ton of fertilizers in the soil in the soil.
        \n\n<b>Planting season</b>
        \nIn Maharashtra, onion and onion are planted in the Kharif season from June to October, during the rabi season from November to February and Summer season from January to June.
        \n\n<b>Varieties:</b>
        \nBaswant 780: This variety is suitable for kharif and rabi season, and the color of this type is dark red. They are larger in medium size onion size. These beings are ready in 100 to 110 days. Hectare yields 250 to 300 quintals.
        \nN-53: This is suitable for kharif season. Made within 100 to 150 days. The color of this caste is reddish. Hectare yields 200 to 250 quintals.
        \nN-2-4-1: This cast is suitable for rabbi season and the color is saffron and dried. Onion is moderately round and the onion stays very well. These beings are ready in 120 to 130 days. Hectare yields 300 to 350 quintals.
        \nPusa Red: Onions are medium-sized reddish brown in red spherical medium. Forming in 120 days from the cultivation. Hectare yields 250 to 300 quintals.
        \n\n<b>Proof of seed:</b>
        \n10 kg seed of onion is enough.
        \n\n<b>Proof of seed:</b>
        \nOnion seedlings, deep spacing of the area which is made of Gadi vapas, can be frozen with the help of two rounds of clans. Raised bed should be 1 cm wide, 3 meters long, 15 cm tall. Choose the blanket in the air and remove it. Draw a line with a 5 cm finger of parallel to the width of the wafer. And sow it in the seed row and cover it with soil. Until the seed is sprouted. Add water to the spring. Water should be given according to the requirement after seeding. In order to control Phulkide and Karpa, 15 liters of monocrotophos and 25 gm of dysthymam in 10 liters of water and 45 gm mixed with 50 grams of urea and 10 ml sediments should be sprayed 4 to 5 sprayers at 10 intervals. Proper planting of plants is considered suitable for plantation.
        \nKharif onion seedlings are ready for 6 to 7 weeks and Rabbi 8 to 9 weeks. Before removing the seedlings Provide enough water for the dip before 24 hours. Onion can be planted on the stove and also on top of the top. Although the ratio of hectare to high speeds is very high, the yield of a medium sized onion is very good. Keep a flat waft two meters wide and keep the waist height. Planting is done in the morning or evening. Plants should be planted at 12.5 by 7.5cm.
        \n\n<b>Fertilizers and water management:</b>
        \nTake 50 grams of nitrogen, 50 kg of phosphorus and 50 kg of potash on the onion crop. After this, give 50kg of Nitrogen per hectare in 1 month. It is important to give regular water to the onion crop. Give the irrigation water at the interval of 10 to 12 days during Kharif season and 6 to 8 days during the summer rabi season.
        \n\n<b>Inter-school:</b>
        \nAfter weeding of the seedlings, weeding should be done in the fields and weeding. To stop the water before 3 weeks before the harvesting, the juice of the leaf comes early in the onion and it is believed to be ready for the harvest.
        \n\n<b>Diseases and pests:</b>
        \nThe main disease on the onion is Karpah, which is a major disease. On the earth, round red spots fall under the rug. The leaves from the sandals look like a burn. The incidence of this disease is very high on kharif onion.
        Flatid or lye hectare very small sized insect pests in the oily surface of the plant. They absorb the juice of sugary juice. So the white dots fall on the surface.
        \n\n<b>Remedy</b>
        \nPhosphomidone 85-WSC per hectare for two to three weeks after the transplantation of flowerkids and corpus diseases. 100 ml or quinolphos 25 is 600 ml or monocrotophos 36 w.c. 550 ml more Diethen M 45, 75 W P. 1250 g or Dieten Z- 78, 75W DP 1000 gm spraying 500 grams of sandwich paste, mixed in 500 liters of water. After the first spraying, spray one spray of three to four weeks. Phosphomidon 85 WSC per hectare during this spraying 100 ml or quinolphos 25 is 600 ml or monocrotophos 36w. S.C. 550 ml more copper oxyclloride 50 w P. 1250 g or dyin z 78, 75 wd. P. Sprinkle 1000 gm in 500 liters of water.
        \n\n<b>Harvesting and production:</b>
        \nAfter harvesting of onion it is ready for harvesting from 3 to 4.5 months. The onion layer of yellow onion grows yellow in yellow and yellow onion. This is called breaking the neck. After the conversion of 60 to 75 percent, consider that the onion extract has matured. The kadali breeders should loose the surrounding lands and loose the onions. After 4-5 days after harvest, keep onion powder in the field and in small dhagya form.
        \nThen cut the onion and vineyards. Cut off the stomach by keeping the stalk of 3 to 4 cm in length. After that, onion should be dry in the shade 4 to 5 days. Hectare yields 250 to 300 quintals.
    </string>


    <!-- Fruits Description -->

    <string name="banana"><b>Introduction</b>
    \nClassical name - Musa Pairadiscaa.
    \nClan - Musseed (Kardali).
    \nParticularly - one-party, molluscum, transmissible, fleshy roots, tropical plants.
    \nNickname - Kardali, Banana, Banana, Rambakkadali, Making.
    \n\n<b>Planting:</b>In terms of area and income, banana is followed by mangoes. India ranks second in the production of bananas. In India, approximately two lakh twenty thousand hectare area is under banana cultivation. Maharashtra is the third largest producer of banana in the field of producing bananas, but in Maharashtra, about 50 percent of Maharashtras first production of commercial production in the business context or in the forecourt is in Maharashtra. Currently, the area is under banana cultivation in the state of Chavala, which covers more than half of the total area. Hence Jalgaon district is considered as a banana.
    \n\n<b>Weather:</b>Banana is a tropical coastal fruit and it enjoys a warm and humid climate. Generally, temperatures ranging from 15 to 40 degrees centigrade are good for this crop. If the winter is less than 12 cents per hectare and summer heat is more than 40 cents above the heat, then the crop is affected.
    \n\n<b>Land:</b>Banana crop is rich in organic material, it is very well-suited, well-grounded, or medium-black, with a depth of up to one meter and good drainage of water. Banana plantations are not suitable for salinity.
    \n\n<b>Castes:</b>Banana has 30 to 40 varieties. Suitable stuff for them to survive, eg. Basrai Harisal Lalveel, Whitewella, Matthi, Vlaa Lalkeli and useful varieties for cooking or cooking, for example Rajalei, Anilal and Ornaments are Rangele.
    \n\n<b>Basarai:</b>These castes are named as Khandeshi, Bhusawal, Vankel, Kabuli, Mauritius, Governor, Loton etc. This is the most important thing in the business of Maharashtra. In Maharashtra, 75% of the total banana area is under cultivation. It is a demand for 5 to 6 ft tall, which is rich in excellent quality and good quality, because of which it is more demanding in the market. These varieties provide warm dry weather. This breed reaches less damages.
    \n\n<b>Harisal:</b>The cultivation of this variety is very high in the Vasai region. The height of this caste is up to 4 meters. This species is thicker and the fruits are dull, and this species is durable. Each log contains 150 to 160 fruits and their weight is 28 to 30 kg. This breed manages marine weather.
    \n\n<b>Lalvalachis:</b>This type of plantation is special in Konkan division. The color of this breed is made of reddish-brown, tall tree, fruit is small and thin, and the taste is mango-sweet and color yellow. There are 200 to 225 fruits in this species. Their weight is about 20 to 22 kg in average. This type of cultivation is much higher than other banana varieties in India.
    \n\n<b>Whitewell:</b>This type of tree is tall, smooth, and the fruit is very small and thin, and its neck is damp. Each time, there are 180 fruits and weighing 15 kg. This type of plantation is found in Thane district.
    \n\n<b>Sleep:</b>This breed tree has a height of five meters, a sturdy trunk, a medium-sized fruit and a poultice, its taste is sweet and delicious. These people become victims of this disease. This type of plantation is found in Ratnagiri area.
    \n\n<b>Rajali:</b>This can be found in large quantities in the caste segment of Konkan. The height of this tree is five meters, the fruit is big and long, in length, it has 80 to 90 fruits. Their weight is 12 to 13 kg. This type of raw fruit is suitable for cooking and sowing well.
    \n\n<b>Bakel:</b>This type of tree is 4 to 5 m tall, the fruit is big, like the size of the young, it is straight and peaked. Each louse has 100 to 150 fruits and weighing 18 to 23 kg. This is useful for caste vegetables. This type of plantation is found in Konkan division.
    \n\n<b>Valla:</b>The height of this tree is two meters and the fruit is thick. The taste of the fruit is sweet to the mangoes. Each species has 80 to 100 fruits and their average weight ranges from 12 to 14 kg. This type of plant is especially found in the Deccan Plateau.
    \n\n<b>Red Kyle:</b>The height of this breed tree is 4 to 5 meters. The fruit is bigger and thick and hard. This caste is red and sandalwood and is thick and dense. It also has tastes sweet. There are about 80 to 100 fruits in each country. Their weight ranges from 13 to 18 kg. In all the varieties of banana this caste is known as a batch.
    \n\n<b>Growth:</b>This crop is cultivated by putting the mouthpiece (sweat) from its holes. During the growth of the main tree, many monkeys grow. There are two main types. 1) Combined with sharp edges and busters, 2) Wide round surface of retail stem. The first type of money is used to increase the weight of coconut from half to one kg.
    \n\n<b>Pre-cultivation:</b>Ironing plowing should be done by rowing plowing on the ground. After that, add 100 watt hectare hectare or compost to the mixture.
    \n\n<b>Planting season:</b>Banana seasoning season varies depending on the weather. Because the effect of the haym is on the growth of banana, the time required for the production of fruit and preparation is the same. The cultivation season begins in the Jalgaon district at the beginning of the monsoon. At this time, the climate in this region is warm and humid.
    \n\n<b>Planting method:</b>When planting, we can plant pots of 0.5 x 0.5 x 0.5 m sized pieces by digging or cutting them. The distance between the two plants is 1.25 1.25 or 1.50 1 and 50 meters for the buses.
    \n\n<b>Fertilizers and fertilizers:</b>The roots of this tree are shallow. Their food demand is high. Therefore, it is important to give the nitrogenic installment during the initial period of growth (for the first month).
    \n\n<b>Kid and Disease:</b>In Banana tree, especially Panama disease, hemp flame, etc. are particularly harmful diseases. The worsening of the kidneys is greatly reduced. The information about disease and pest problems is summarized below.
    \n\n<b>Garden care:</b>Keep the ground floor clean and fried. For this, initial scrub should be given. Next should be to paint by hand.
    \nKeep the ground floor clean and fried. For this, initial scrub should be given. Next should be to paint by hand.\nMany bananas are grown in the banana belt. Remove it from time to time.\nApply 4 to 5 months after planting on the soil of the plant.\nProvide support to the plant if necessary.
    \n\n<b>Manure Management:</b>\n<b>Water management:</b> - 10 kg per plant or 5 kg per plant of vermicelli fertilizer
    \n<i>Organic fertilizers</i> - Azospirillum - 25 gm per tree and PSB at 25 gram per year during the banana plantation
    \n<i>Bio-fertilizers</i> - 200 gm per plant for banana is recommended to give 40 gm phosphorus and 200 gms of potash. To give them effective fertilization while giving chemical fertilizers to the soil, give deep briquetry to the fertilizers and give them the fertilizer.
    \n\n<i>Chemical fertilizers</i>Banana crops total 1800 to 2200 min. M Needs water. Drip irrigation is very useful for banana, and it is more suitable for drip irrigation (microtubes) dripper or inline dripper than the micro-tube system. Speed of evaporation, increase in the ratio of land, etc. Banana needs water on matters.
    </string>

    <string name="orange"><b>Introduction:</b>
The Nagpur Saratra of Sandra in Maharashtra is famous for its amazing taste. Concentrates are cultivated mainly in Vidarbha. Farmers of western Maharashtra and Marathwada also have the opportunity to cultivate orangery.

\n\n<b>Weather:</b>
Increase the orange tree from 13 to 37 degrees. Gray This is excellent in the temperature range. Heat and slightly humid weather, this crop yields 370m I Plant growth is good for 50 to 53 percent air humidity
\n\n<b>Land:</b>
Moderate black soil of 1 to 1.5 m, under which soil moist soil or a few limestone or sand-mixed soil, and the acidic index of the soil ranges from 5.5 to 7.5. Plant cultivation of such lands is best understood. Heavy black lands, in which black soil is 1.5 to 3.5 meters deep and there is a layer of sticking soil. Because of the ability to hold water in such a large quantity of water, the trees are dried after due to excessive amount of water. Therefore, do not plant orange plant in such a type of soil.
\n\n<b>Predetermined:</b>
After planting the orange garden, after the selection of the land, make the soil deep. Narmamatha, Harali, Kas and Kunda should be taken from the roots. The land should be fried by keeping the clay. If there is fluctuation, then bring the land to the level of equilibrium.
\n\n<b>Selection of Colors:</b>
Organic plantation is done through artificial cloths. While selecting the pen, it should be filled with eyes full of scientifically healthy, kind, vigorous, growing, zamble, or colorful lemon. Treatment of oranges should be taken from agriculture universities and government nurses.
\n\n<b>Castes:</b>
Orange orangra orangra, orange orange and no. There are 182 species of these species.
\n\n<b>Preparation for cultivation:</b>
60 x 60 x 60 cm at 6 x 6 meters distance for the cultivation of this crop. I Plate the area with a square patch and square it in a square manner. Dig a pit before one month before cultivation. These pits should be done by mixing 25 kg of good debris, 2 kg of single super phosphate more than 100 gm, 10% chlorine / Oldton powder, and good soil or clay soil on the soil surface before rainy season.
\n\n<b>Water:</b>
Generally, an orange system has to be adjusted to 24 to 25 oily a year. At intervals of 8 to 10 days in Hivwaly. In the summer of 6 to 7 days in the summer, it should be applied as per the requirement. Ring the ring in order to make oats and give water to the outside. Because the tree-eating and water-intensive children are spread across the tree areas. Due to this method, there is no water from the plant. Therefore, disease like disease like diarrhea helps in reducing the incidence of diseases.
\n\n<b>Fertilizer:</b>
The orange tree should be given as per the age of fertilizer as per the age.
During the growth of the above fertilizers, the fertilizer should be given in the last week of the month of May or in the first week of June and the chemical fertilizers divided into 3 equal installments during the first 1 to 5 years, in the months of July, September and February. Wrappers should be mixed in soil with bundle method. If the soil needs to be tested and given as per the requirement of potash, then give it accordingly

    </string>

    <string name="mangeo">

    </string>

    <string name="apple">
    There are more than 8,000 different varieties of apples. Most are bred for their taste and utilitarian use, including cooking and cider production.
\n Apple trees are generally produced by grafting (attaching a piece of an existing tree to a root stock to form a new tree) or from seeds.
One benefit of grafted trees is they will bear fruit much more quickly than those grown from seed- with grafted trees, you can even get a tree that bears fruit the first year.
        \n\n <b>Some popular varieties of apple trees include:</b>
\n Honeycrisp Apple Trees
\n Fuji Apple Trees
\n Gala Apple Trees
\n Red Delicious Apple Trees
\n Granny Smith Apple Trees
\n Pink Lady Apple Trees
\n Golden Delicious Apple Trees
\n McIntosh Apple Trees
\n\n <b>What types of apple trees should you plant?</b>
\n Ideally, your apple orchard (no matter how big or small it is) will be in production for many years. In order to protect your investment and bear fruit, it’s important to choose the right apple trees to suit your needs and climate.
\n\n <b>How do you select the right apple trees for your garden? </b>
        \n It depends on a few different things, including your climate and hardiness zone, landscape, how many apple trees you want to plant and which varieties.
        \n Below are a few considerations:
\n\n <b>Apple trees for different climates</b>
\n <b>Want to plant apple trees in a colder climate? </b>
         \n You will want to find apple tree varieties well-suited to Northern areas.
        \n In a warmer climate? Check out apple trees that are best for Southern.
        \nIf you are on the West Coast, you will want to choose from Western apple trees.
        \nMost apples fall within two or more different groups, so it is easy to find the right apple tree as well as a companion pollinator that will thrive in the same climate.
\n <b>Apple tree sizes</b>
\n Apple trees come in many different sizes, from full-size trees to dwarf trees that grow 8-10 feet tall. You will want to evaluate the size of your planting area to determine what apple variety is best - and remember, in most cases, you will want to leave room for at least two apple trees, if not more.
\n\n <b>How big do you want your apple trees to get? </b> \n Keep in mind that apple trees contain three parts: the branches, the trunk, and the root system.
\n Our dwarf apple trees are grafted for a more controlled size. Most dwarf trees maintain heights of between 10 to 15 feet, which make them easier for fitting into small landscapes and easily picking fruit.
\n <b>Working with an even smaller area? </b>
        \n Consider a new variety like columnar apple trees - designed to grow upright without horizontal branching, they are perfect for small spaces and even patios or balconies.
\n <b>Apple tree flavor</b>
\n Think about your favorite flavors and what you like to taste in apples - do you like sweeter apples, or more tart? Once you figure out what type of apples you like, think about how you plan to use your apples. Are you planning on snacking, baking, juicing or canning? Dessert apples are best for eating fresh, whereas culinary apples are best for cooking. Some apples have to be eaten within a few days of being picked, while others can be stored for a month or more before eating – and can actually improve in flavor over time. For example, Red Delicious Apples are one of the sweetest cultivars available.
\n Youyou willll also need to consider how many trees you need to plant. If you want to grow several trees, that can affect the specific types of trees you purchase. Different varieties can ripen at different times, from late summer to late fall, and different varieties are required to pollinate specific apple trees.
\n <b>Where should apple trees be planted?</b>
\n Most apple trees grow best in a warm climate with full sunlight  and good air circulation. The best spot is typically on the north side of a house or treeline.
\n Apple trees need well-draining soil, and light- to medium-textured soils work best - apple trees typically do not thrive in heavy clay soil. Avoid any areas where cold might settle in lower areas, and avoid planting near wooded areas or other trees that might block sun.
\n <b>If you are planting an apple tree in a Northern state:</b>
\n It is best to choose early to mid-season varieties that will ripen in an area with a shorter growing season.
\n <b>If you are planting an apple tree in a Southern state:</b>
\n We recommend finding a sheltered space facing the Southern part of your garden. Planting the trees near a hedge or wall can help protect the trees from wind damage.
\n <b>When should apple trees be planted?</b>

\n Apple trees are very hardy. They can withstand most conditions, including extreme cold and wind. It is typically best to plant your apple trees during the spring - however, if you live in an area with mild autumns and your winter months have moisture in the air, they can be planted in the fall. In that case, ensure you plant six weeks prior to first frost so the tree can establish properly before winter.
\n <b>Apple tree diseases</b>
\n While apple trees are very hard, there are a few diseases that may affect apple trees. The best defense is a healthy tree. Maintaining proper soil conditions, adequate water levels, and fertilization can help your trees thrive.
\n <b>Here are a few diseases to avoid:</b>
\n <b>Fire blight</b>
\n Fire blight is a bacterial disease that causes branches to blacken, giving them a scorched look, and will kill the tree eventually. You can control this blight by either choosing trees that are genetically resistant to the disease, or removing blighted branches off the tree.
\n <b>Powdery mildew</b>
\n Powdery mildew attacks the foliage and fruit on apple trees. It is a white fungus that will appear on the leaves, fruit, and flowers. If left untreated, it will eventually cause the tree’s health to decline. You can help control this disease by applying a fungicide to the tree during early spring, just as the leaves are starting to push out.
\n <b>Apple scab</b>

        \n An apple scab is a fungus that leaves black soot-like spots on the leaves and fruit. This disease mostly affects new leaves in the spring, during moist conditions. However, it can affect mature leaves during May and early June.
\n The fungus appears as black velvety spots on the leaves. As a result, the leaves turn yellow and eventually drop.You can control this disease by either choosing disease-resistant apples, or applying fungicides as the leaves come out during the spring.
\n <b>Cedar apple rust</b>
\n Cedar apple rust is a fungus that leaves rusty spots on the leaves of the tree. This disease commonly affects Juniper, Cedar, and Apple Trees. When this fungus attacks Apple Trees, the leaves will develop small yellow spots in late spring. As the tree becomes more stressed, both leaves and fruit will drop off the tree prematurely. Cedar Apple Rust cannot be controlled once the tree is infected.
\n <b>Apple tree care and planting tips</b>
\n <b>What is the best soil for apple trees?</b>
\n Apple trees can tolerate a wide range of soil types, but they prefer well-drained soil with high acidity. We recommend planting them in rich soil. Your apple tree will benefit most from being fertilized yearly with a 10-10-10 formula. Fertilizer is especially helpful if you notice that the tree’s leaves are pale in color, or that the tree has grown less than inches per year.
\n <b>How much should you water your apple trees?</b>
\n Apples trees are hearty trees that do not require much care when they are first planted, and they often thrive without much water once they become established. However, if you live in a dry area or experience a prolonged period of drought, we recommend 4 to 6 inches of water every couple of weeks. Apple trees thrive best in full sun, for at least 6 to 8 hours per day.
\n <b>How to protect your apple tree</b>

        \n <b>There are a few preventative steps you can take to maintain your tree’s health:</b>
\n <b>Apply a fungicide spray on growing trees</b>
\n This will help reduce the likelihood of infection spreading from surrounding junipers, cedars and apple trees.
\n <b>Remove dead, damaged, or diseased branches</b>
\n This includes suckers - the shoots that come up from the roots or base of your tree. You can also treat your trees with insecticide to help prevent these diseases from occurring.
\n <b> Why is my apple tree not producing fruit?</b>
\n Apple trees can have good and bad years. This is another good reason to have more than one tree, even if your tree is self-fertile. At times, a tree may have very few blossoms, even when the spring weather is good. This can often be caused by incorrect pruning during the previous summer. The tree may also have trouble bearing fruit due to prolonged stress from lack of water or nutrients. Giving your tree adequate water and fertilizer will help prevent this issue.



    </string>

    <string name="greps"><b>Introduction:</b>
        There is a mention in the Bible about the production of a Nova granulated vineyard . Plena (E. 23-79), the Roman scientist has described 91 types of grape varieties, there are several types of alcoholic beverages and 50 varieties of grape varieties.
        \n\n<b>Area of cultivation</b>
        Grape production is more than any other fruit in the global production of fruits. In the world of 1972 9 8 odds. The area was under the grape. 80% of the product is used for making liquor, 13% for eating and 7% for raisins and currant preparation. France, Italy, Spain, Turkey and Russia are the major grappling countries. The United States of America, Algeria, Romania, Argentina, Greece and Portugal are the other countries. Iran, Afghanistan, D. Even in Africa and Australia, it is cultivated for a very large number of trees. In India, it was in 967-68. 8,000 people were in this area and they were in the world.
        \n\n<b>Land and climate:</b>
        Good drift, light or medium black or 60-90 cm The land, which is deep and underneath, is very suitable for planting. The water drain is very important in this crop. The subtropical region is favorable for grape cultivation. Long-term, hot, dry-dry (non-rain) summer season is essential for this crop. Rainfall in just 3-4 months a year, 3,000 m in the periods of hot and dry climate.
        \n\n<b>Planting:</b>
        There are two methods for planting grapes. After preparing the same brush papers, they get straight into the field in the month of October. At one place, the two small pen should be 10-15 cm. Get interrupted. She roses vine 30-45 cm Upon increasing, after placing one section of them vigorously, one is removed. The second method is 30X15 cm in October. The cuttings applied at the distance from two to two and a half months after the flowering of the vine begins to grow, in their regular place in January. At that time, the vine can be taken carefully by the boards of the soil of the soil. Now fill the soil in plastic bags and fill the clogs in it. And they can be put to a permanent place after they are destroyed. Get rid of the vine lines south-east.
        \n\n<b>Fertilizer:</b>
        Because of the abundance of the crop every year, the vineyards absorb very large amount of nutrients from the soil. To compensate them, it is necessary to give fertilizers and fertilizers to the farmers. April and October, after pruncation, lots of quantities given after the April pruning. The method of turnaround, type of vine, fruit capacity and the type of soil have been taken into account in terms of these factors, and according to fertilizer, it has been decidedly as fertilizer.
        \n\n<b>Disease:</b>
        Grapes are bury, kayvada and karpa, which are important fungal diseases (there are chronic diseases like chlorofluorant).
        \n\n<b>Generate:</b>
        Grape variety depends on the type of grape variety, rich nutrients, proper weather, systematic planting, turning on the basis, pruning and cultivation, protection of diseases from diseases and pests. Income reduces in first year But they grow from next year. Generally, 10-15 ton grapes are obtained in Maharashtra. The average yield of grape in India is more than 10 tons of hectare, and is much higher than Californias income and more than the major countries in the world of grappling plants like France, Italy and Spain.

    </string>

    <string name="pineapple"><b>Introduction:</b>
        The famous caddy bush 1 · 5 m High and biconous is native to South America. In Brazil, wild species are found, the name Ananas is given to the black Indian Indians, and Spanish and Portuguese people planted it in tropical countries. Its general physical symptoms are described in Bommelescis family . Tokas 1m There is a bunch of narrow, long, stout, thick, tough, thorny banks and edges The flower comes from it. Flowers are many, small breezes, and shrub leaves come again with a shrub leaf and many buds (cadaars) come in the bottom. A common liver fruit of whole grainsBante (falcoj) The flowers are surrounded by many axes in the juicy axis of flowering, flowering roofs, sandalwood and glossy [flowers]. This is sold by pineapple It usually looks like a pine tree cone, so the English name Pineapple is derived.
        \nPlow the land, plow it up Rainwater harvesting starts at the beginning of monsoon and in the winter, in the winter, in two rows, one to one and a half meters. And one to one and a half in one row. Keep distance apart. Crop yields sufficient water, 12 tons of hectare for hectare and kharif in March, June, July and September. Also 50-80 kg Nitrogen, 25-40 kg Phosphorus and 50-80 kg Potassium or nitrogen, phosphorus and potassium is 12: 6: 12 in size with a mixture of 540-900 kgs. After planting, they will be divided into 2-3 parts. Generally, flowers grow in flowers during February to April and fruits grow as early as July and September.
        \n\n<b>Generate:</b>
        Pineapple yield depends on land, cultivation, fertilizer, water, breeds etc. The maximum world income of hectares is up to 100 tons in Hawaii In India, it can be used as an average one-and-a-half tons but the Q breed comes to fifty-five tons.
        After four or five years of normal cultivation, fruits are larger. The pineapple plant that is planted in the mountainous area of Assam, continues till 20 to 30 years.
        \n\n<b>Use:</b>
        B vitamins are B and in excess quantity. Eat fruits as they eat freshly. Qgoing to cabinets in cabinets is very good. The fruits are made of fruit juices, marmalas, sticks, infusion and syrup. Generally, the two pages that have been grown for two years, are hand-painted White Pine Fiber called white, glossy, strong, durable, and silk thread, and make Pinnakapad (China, Formosa, and the Philippines Islands). In India, pineapples are used for round gums.
        \n\n<b>Disease:</b>
        Pineapple is found in falcon and rarely Khodakuj. Falcus is a disease caused by Saradostomella Paradoxa poison [fungus] most likely to harvest or transport the fruit Therefore, fruits fall degradation and scavengers. Therefore, do not let them hurt when cutting fruit and take care while transporting. Disease is caused by phytoprophora parasitic fever. Due to not causing disease, drainage the soil from the soil.
        Pumpkin worms cause nuisance of this pest. Dyesynon is used for this.

    </string>

    <string name="papaya">\n\n<b>Introduction:</b>
    \nPapaya is a continuous green leafy fruit tree. They were brought to the 16th century in India. Now it was planted in the Hawaii Islands, Sri Lanka, South Africa, Malaysia, Australasia, the Philippines Islands and India. The dry and rainy weather of India and 1,300m from the sea. Papaya can grow in the area of high altitude. As per available information, the total area of papaya cultivation in India is 10,848 ha. And the maximum area (3,880 ha.) Is in the state of Bihar. Assam has 2,041 ha., Madhya Pradesh has 2,000 hectares. And Maharashtra and Gujarat together 1,236 Area and 1,417 in otherstates. Is the area.
    \n\n<b>Weather:</b>
    \nPapaya growth is good in dry dry weather and proper water supply. 2°C PAPI does not believe in the temperature below. The fruits produced in cold weather are tasteless.
    \n\n<b>Land:</b>
    \nPaddy cultivation is good, free of water well, and plenty of bio-food supply. Paddy in the middle black soil of the southern part of India, as well as in the field of sand, increases the papaya. The lack of rustic limestone and lack of biomass and good black and white soil is not good. In the case of this crop, water drainage is very important. If the drainage is not properly done, then the stomach rust causes irritation.
    \n\n<b>Planting:</b>
    \nSeedlings are planted and planted. Planting of plowing, ditching, dredging, etc., in the early rainy season and rainy season in monsoon in less rainy areas.
    \n\n<b>Preparation of seedlings:</b>
    \nGood people take a full seed of fruit seed bearing fruit, and they are washed and cleaned and stored in a shade by drying it. Fresh seeds are always good for seedlings. Before the planting season Seed two weeks for the plants. 250 gms of seedlings to be planted in one hectare area B is enough. B. Generally, they are installed in the bedroom. Seedlings 9 - 12 cm After the height, they can be removed from the stomach and kept in a permanent place in the prepared area. Two pits of 2-3 m We keep planting plants by keeping distance. There is no difference between male and female in plantation conditions. There are 40-60 tectonic plants grown in the planted plants. The rest are narzed. The yield in a particular area is reduced because the stalk does not produce fruits. To avoid this, you can put two or three seedlings in one or two slopes. If the seedlings grow and they flower, then the difference between male and female can be identified. After placing two or four pods in the entire garden, the remaining chana trees are cut off. Therefore, there is more than average female seedlings in the cultivation.

    </string>

    <string name="watermelon">

    </string>


    <!-- Soils Description -->
    <string name="loam">
        \n<b>Loam</b> — This type of soil helps grow the best possible crops because it provides the necessary elements. Loamy sand contains mostly sand plus clay and silt. It is good for root vegetables, such as carrots and beets, leafy vegetables, and tomatoes.
    </string>
    <string name="clay">
        \n<b>Clay</b> — Cabbage and broccoli grow well in clay soil, but it may not be good for root vegetables because of its dense texture, writes D. Laverne O’Neal in Hunker. Cherry, pear, maple, and black walnut trees also thrive in clay soil. Edible herbs, including yarrow and red valerian, also benefit from it.
    </string>
    <string name="sand">
      \n<b>Sand</b> — Root vegetables, including turnips, parsnips, and carrots, grow well in sandy soil as do pomegranate and fig trees. Bush clover, bayberry, creeping juniper, and thyme are among the herbs that do well in sandy soil.
        \n\n<b>Soil texture:</b>Quartz is the predominant mineral in the sand fraction of most soils. Sand particles have a relatively small surface area per unit weight, low water retention and little chemical activity compared with silt and clay.
    </string>
    <string name="silt">
        \n<b>Silt</b> — Silty soil is fertile and offers nutrients for development. Lettuce, cabbage, carrots, turnips, and many other vegetables flourish in silt. Strawberries, raspberries, blackberries, citrus trees, and pomegranate trees also develop well in silt.
        \n\n<b>Soil texture</b>Silt has a relatively limited surface area and little chemical activity. Soils high in silt may compact under heavy traffic and this affects the movement of air and water in the soil.
    </string>
    <string name="peat">
        \n<b>Peat</b> — Peaty soil provides growth when mixed with rich organic matter, lime, and compost that reduces its acidity, according to Eartheasy. Legumes, root crops, cabbage, and spinach are easily grown in soil that’s well-drained.
     </string>
    <string name="chalk">
        \n<b>Chalk</b> — Sweet corn, beets, spinach, and cabbage are among the vegetables that benefit from more chalky soil. It is recommended that farmers use fertilizers and balance the pH levels to deal with the alkaline that can sometimes stunt growth.
    \n\n<b>Soil texture</b>Clays have very large surface areas compared with the other inorganic fractions. As a result clays are chemically very active and are able to hold nutrients on their surfaces. These nutrients can be released into soil water from where they can be used by plants. Like nutrients, water also attaches to the surfaces of clays but this water can be hard for plants to use.
    There are many different types of clays. The ability of clays to swell and to retain a shape into which they have been formed, as well as their sticky nature, distinguish them from sand and silt.
    </string>
    <string name="email_subject">email_subject</string>
    <string name="email_body">email_body</string>
    <string name="send_to">send_to</string>
    <string name="send_email">send_email</string>
    <string name="topbg">topbg</string>
    <string name="webUrl">https://nurserylive.com/</string>
    <string name="webUrl2">https://nurserylive.com/</string>


</resources>